Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series IX
    - Wald - Correspondence re: Interviews, Research, Information, 1966 (Box 334, Folder 194)
    - Library - Reserve Shelf Lists, 1961-66 (Box 334, Folder 195)
    - Budget, 1961-62 (Box 334, Folder 196)
    - Budget, 1963-(J:4 (Box 334, Folder 197)
    - Yale School of Nursing Alumnae Fund, 1965-66 (Box 334, Folder 198)
    - Ph.D. Program Development, 1962 (Box 334, Folder 199)
    - Faculty Research Symposium, 1964-65 (Box 334, Folder 201)
    - Yale School of Nursing Alumnae Association, 1965-66 (Box 334, Folder 202)
    - Suggestions for YSN Lecture, 1965-66 (Box 334, Folder 203)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Research Teaching, Undated (Box 334, Folder 204)
    - Committee on Ethics for Publication, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 205)
    - Committee on Ethics of Research, 1965 (Box 335, Folder 206)
    - Library Committee (Dean's Office), 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 207)
    - Library Committee. (Dean's Office), 1965-66 (Box 335, Folder 208)
    - Student Progress committee, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 209)
    - Recording Devices Committee, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 210)
    - Admissions Committee, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 211)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Public Health, Nursing, 1964 (Box 335, Folder 212)
    - Yale School of Nursing Lecture Series, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 213)
    - Connnittee to Establish Clinical Practice for YSN Faculty, 1964-65 (Box 335, Folder 214)
    - U.S. Air Force, 1967 (Box 335, Folder 215)
    - Dean Taylor's Exhibit, 1965 (Box 335, Folder 216)
    - Dean Search Committee, Correspondence, Minutes, 1966 (Box 335, Folder 217)
    - Dean Search committee, Curriculum Vitae, 1966-67 (Box 335, Folder 218)
    - YSN Nursing Theory Seminar, 1966 (Box 335, Folder 219)
    - Schedules, Permanent File Copies, 1957-66 (Box 335, Folder 220)
  - Series X
    - American Hospital Association - Hospital Research and Educational Trust, Meeting, Chicago, OCT 2. 1967 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - American Hospital Association - Hospital Research and Educational Trust, 1967-68 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - Alumnae College, 1964-69 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - American Journal of Nursing, 1969-71 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - American Red Cross, 1968-70 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - American Nurses Association, Convention, Dallas, 1968 MAY (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - Yale School of Nursing Annual Report, 1967-68 (Box 336, Folder 7)
    - American Public Health Association - general, 1967-68 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Audiovisual Aids, 1965-69 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Colleges attended by graduates of Yale School of Nursing graduate program, 1967 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Columbia Point Health Center, 1967-68 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - Commencement, 1968 (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, 1969 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - Community Affairs, 1968 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Community Health Services, 1969-70 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - Comprehensive Health Care for Children in the Hill
      - Dean, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 17)
      - Yale School of Nursing, 1967 (Box 337, Folder 18)
    - Conant, Lucy - Farewell Party, Harkness Lounge, 1968 January 11 (Box 337, Folder 19)
    - Connecticut League for Nursing, 1969-70 (Box 337, Folder 20)
      - Board of Directors, 1969-70 (Box 337, Folder 21)
      - Board of Directors, 1968-69 (Box 337, Folder 22)
    - Connecticut Nurses' Association, 1969 (Box 338, Folder 23)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1968 (Box 338, Folder 24)
    - Connecticut Reginnal Medical Planning (Dr. H. Clark), 1969-71 (Box 338, Folder 25)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Planning (Dr. H. Clark), 1967-69 (Box 338, Folder 26)
    - Continuing Care Unit, 1968-70 (Box 339, Folder 27)
    - Dixwell Legal Rights Association, 1969 (Box 339, Folder 28)
    - Fair Haven Project, 1969 (Box 339, Folder 29)
    - Frontier Nursing Service, 1969-70 (Box 339, Folder 31)
    - Hill Health Center, 1967-69 (Box 339, Folder 32)
    - Allied Health Professions Training, 1969 (Box 339, Folder 33)
    - Concepts in Nursing Course, N-140, 1968 (Box 339, Folder 34)
    - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1968 (Box 339, Folder 35-36)
    - Community Health Care Center Plan, 1968-69 (Box 340, Folder 37)
    - Dr. Redlich's Committee on Chairmanship of Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1967-68 (Box 340, Folder 38)
    - Committee on Community Health Services, 1968-69 (Box 340, Folder 39)
    - Curriculum Committee Minutes (Faculty), 1969-70 (Box 340, Folder 40)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1967-69 (Box 340, Folder 41)
    - Executive Council (Dean's Office), 1968 (Box 340, Folder 42)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1968-69 (Box 341, Folder 43)
    - Faculty Committee, 1967-68 (Box 341, Folder 44)
    - Faculty Research Committee, 1968-69 (Box 341, Folder 45)
    - Inquiries (Miscellaneous), 1969 (Box 341, Folder 46)
    - Inquiries (Miscellaneous), 19G8 (Box 341, Folder 47)
    - International, 1965-69 (Box 341, Folder 48)
    - International Junior of Nursing Studies, 1968-69 (Box 341, Folder 49)
    - International Council of Nurses (ICN), 1969-70 (Box 341, Folder 50)
    - Joint Administrative Committee, 1968-69 (Box 341, Folder 51)
    - Joint Administrative Committee (Dean's Office), 1967-68 (Box 341, Folder 52)
    - Macmillan Company, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 54)
    - Haster's Reports Committee, 1967-69 (Box 342, Folder 55)
    - Medical Center Health Report Committee on Health Careers, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 56)
    - Medical Center Planning Group, 1967-68 (Box 342, Folder 57)
    - National League for Nursing - General, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 59)
    - National League for Nursing Accreditation Review, 1968 (Box 342, Folder 60)
    - National League for Nursing Convention, Detroit, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 61)
    - Proposal Submitted to ANF: "Two Encounters of Mother and New Born," Sharon Schindler, 1969 (Box 342, Folder 62)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Program, 1967-1968 (Box 343, Folder 63)
    - Psychiatric Nursing Faculty, 1967-68 (Box 343, Folder 64)
    - Psychiatric Nurse Specialist Recruitment, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 65-66)
    - Grant Application: Research in Nursing Care, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 68)
    - Study on Referral Systems, R. Mazer, 1969 (Box 343, Folder 69)
    - Exploratory Curriculum Grant, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 71)
    - Visitors to Yale School of Nursing, 1967-68 (Box 343, Folder 72)
    - United States Public Health Service Construction Grants, 1968 (Box 343, Folder 73)
    - National Institute for Mental Health Grant # 5 Tl MH-7903-06 (IBM No. 9580-49-48907) (Psychiatric nursing), 1967-68 (Box 343, Folder 74)
    - Professional Nurse Traineeship Grant, NT-36-C 11, 9580-49-48901, 1967-68 (Box 343, Folder 75)
    - Scholarships for Graduate Students, 1967-69 (Box 343, Folder 76)
    - Tavistock Conference, 1968 MAR (Box 344, Folder 78)
    - Student Health Organization, 1968-69 (Box 344, Folder 79)
    - United States Public Health Service Grant Proposal, Elsberry-Mazer, 1968-69 (Box 344, Folder 80)
    - Potential Faculty, 1965-66 (Box 344, Folder 81)
    - Proposed names for new faculty members, 1959-67 (Box 344, Folder 82)
    - Potential Faculty -Clinical Expert in Obstetric Nursing, 1964-65 (Box 344, Folder 83)
    - Potential Faculty, Statistics, 1967 (Box 344, Folder 84)
    - Recruitment for Research Position, 1965 (Box 344, Folder 85)
    - Potential Faculty -Social Scientist, 1964-65 (Box 344, Folder 86)
    - Potential Assistants in Research, 1957 (Box 344, Folder 87)
    - Applications for Faculty Positions, Psychiatric Program, 1968 (Box 344, Folder 88)
      Restricted until January 1, 2043
    - Recruitment of Public Health Nursing Faculty Member, 1966-68 (Box 344, Folder 89)
    - Study Design Consultant, 1962 (Box 344, Folder 90)
    - Potential Faculty, 1967-68 (Box 344, Folder 91)
    - Applicants for Positions, 1959-69 (Box 344, Folder 92)
      Restricted until January 1, 2044
    - Potential Personnel, Assistant to the Dean for Student Affairs, 1964 (Box 344, Folder 93)
      Restricted until January 1, 2039
    - Correspondence with Potential Faculty in Methods of Research, 1964 (Box 345, Folder 94)
    - Potential Faculty - Maternity, 1964-67 (Box 345, Folder 95)
    - Recruitment - Director of Nursing, Mental Health Center, 1965 (Box 345, Folder 96)
    - Potential Applicants, 1967-70 (Box 345, Folder 97)
    - Correspondence with Potential Faculty in Methods of Research, 1960 (Box 345, Folder 98)
    - Proposed Names for Position (Psychiatric Nursing), 1961-66 (Box 345, Folder 99)
    - Director for Yale Psychiatric Institute with Yale School of Nursing Appointment, 1963-66 (Box 345, Folder 100)
    - Yale School of Nursing Reference Room - Administrative and Miscellaneous Records, 1969 (Box 345, Folder 101-102)
    - Student Curriculum Committtee, 1967-70 (Box 346, Folder 103)
    - Universities A-K (Correspondence), 1968-70 (Box 346, Folder 104-105)
    - Universities I-Z (Correspondence), 1968-70 (Box 346, Folder 106)
    - United Stetes Public Health Service - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 346, Folder 107)
    - United States Public Health Service - Bureau of Health Manpower, 1967-68 (Box 346, Folder 109)
    - World Health Organization (WHO), Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 346, Folder 110)
    - Yale University - Comptroller, 1968 (Box 346, Folder 111)
    - Yale - Employee Relations Department (Personnel), 1967-68 (Box 347, Folder 112)
    - Yale - Office of University Development, 1968-69 (Box 347, Folder 113)
    - Yale - Grant and Contract Administration (Mr. Hoskins, Director), 1967-69 (Box 347, Folder 114)
    - Yale University Department of Health, 1968-69 (Box 347, Folder 115)
    - Health Services Research Centers, 1967-68 (Box 347, Folder 116-117)
    - Yale -Housing, 1968-69 (Box 347, Folder 118)
    - Yale Medical Librarian (Mr. Truelson), 1969 (Box 347, Folder 119)
    - Yale -Library and Medical Library Committee, 1967-72 (Box 347, Folder 120)
    - Yale -International Student Center, 143 Elm Street, 1967-68 (Box 347, Folder 121)
    - Yale Medical Center Planning, 1968-69 (Box 347, Folder 122)
    - Yale Interprofessional Education, 1969 (Box 347, Folder 123)
    - Yale Graduate School, (J.P. Miller), 1966-69 (Box 347, Folder 124)
    - Yale -Epidemiology and Public Health, Department of Health Education Progress, 1968-69 (Box 348, Folder 125)
    - Yale -Faculty Personnel Policies, 1967-69 (Box 348, Folder 126)
    - Yale -An Institution for WOMEN AT YALE -Coeducation (Box 348, Folder 127)
    - Yale School of Nursing -Mental Health Center Relationships, 1967-69 (Box 348, Folder 128)
    - Yale School of Nursing -Leases HNHC Building, 1966-69 (Box 348, Folder 129)
    - Yale Business Office (J. Embersitis), 1966-69 (Box 348, Folder 130)
    - Yale Child Study Center, 1966-69 (Box 348, Folder 131)
    - Yale - College Work Study Program, 1969 (Box 348, Folder 132)
    - Yale -Dean F. C. Redlich, 1969 (Box 348, Folder 133)
    - Yale New Raven Medical Center, Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 348, Folder 134)
    - Yale University Miscellaneous, 1967-68 (Box 348, Folder 135)
    - Yale University, Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 348, Folder 136-137)
    - Yale -Report of Study Group on Nursing Education, 1968 (Box 348, Folder 138)
  - Series XI
    - American Association of Deans of College and Universities Schools of Nursing, 1969-71 (Box 349, Folder 1)
    - Yale School of Nursing Alumnae College, 1968-70 (Box 349, Folder 2)
    - 11th Alumnae College (YSN), 1968-70 (Box 349, Folder 3)
    - Yale School of Nursing Alumnae Association, 1967-68 (Box 349, Folder 4)
    - Yale School of Nursing Annual Report, 1969 (Box 349, Folder 5)
    - A Nurse's Study of Care for Dying Patients," F.S. Wald, Gr. # NU00352-01, 1969 (Box 349, Folder 6)
    - Wald Grant, NU 00352-01 (9580-49-50562), 1970 (Box 349, Folder 7)
    - Studies in Nurse Patient Interaction, D. Diers, NU 00179-06, 1970-71 (Box 349, Folder 8)
    - Studies in Nurse Patient Interaction, D. Diers, NU 63179-05, 1969-70 (Box 350, Folder 9)
    - Studies in Nurse Patient Interaction, D. Diers, NU00179-04, 1968-71 (Box 350, Folder 10)
    - NU 00323-01 (9580-49-50158) J. Barrett's Study -Accounts, 1969-70 (Box 350, Folder 11)
    - NU 00323-02, J. Barrett, The Nurse Specialist and Hospital Organization, 1967-71 (Box 350, Folder 12)
    - Accounts, NU 00228-01 (Johnson), 1967-68 (Box 350, Folder 13)
    - NU 00323-01 Nurse Specialist and Hospital Organization (J.Barrett), 1968-69 (Box 350, Folder 14)
    - Research Development Grant, -U 00314-02, 1969-70 (Box 350, Folder 15)
    - Nurse-Practitioner Study NIH 70-4001 (9580-49-44614) Statements, 1969-72 (Box 350, Folder 16)
    - Nurse Practitioner Study, NIH 4001 (Invoices etc.), 1969-72 (Box 350, Folder 17-18)
    - Faculty Research Development Grant, NU 00063-06, 1967-70 (Box 351, Folder 19)
    - Research Development Project, NU 00314-01 (Accounts), 1969 (Box 351, Folder 20)
    - NIH 70-4001 Contract -Correspondence, 1969-72 (Box 351, Folder 21)
    - Public Health Service Division of Nursing, Contract NIH 70-4001 (P), 1969 (Box 351, Folder 22)
    - Study of Psychiatric Nursing, Theory and Practice (Psychiatric Institutes) Accounts, 1970 (Box 351, Folder 23)
    - National Institute of Mental Health Proposal: A Program for Studying Psychiatric Nursing &Demands for Mental Health Care, Submitted, 1968 (Box 351, Folder 24)
    - NIMH 7903-08 (9580-49-50186), 1969-70 (Box 351, Folder 25)
    - Mental Health Training Grant NIMH 7903-09, 1970-71 (Box 352, Folder 28)
    - United States Public Health Service Grant Proposal Nu 00220 (M. Fischelis), 1966-68 (Box 352, Folder 29)
    - NU 00220-02 (Fischelis), 1968-69 (Box 352, Folder 30)
    - Nursing Studies Index Project (Miss Henderson), 1965-73 (Box 352, Folder 31)
    - Student Strike and Demonstrations (Additional 1/17/78), 1970 MAY (Box 352, Folder 32)
    - Petty Cash and Remittance Slip Reports, 1968-71 (Box 352, Folder 34)
    - Expense Budget, 1969-70 (Box 352, Folder 35)
    - Budget, 1969-70 (Box 353, Folder 36)
    - Budget - Correspondence and copies of Corporation vote, 1968-69 (Box 353, Folder 37)
    - Budget Worksheets, 1969-70 (Box 353, Folder 38)
    - Budget (Statement of Accounts), 1972 (Box 353, Folder 39)
    - Maternity Institutes (9580-49-74329), 1967-70 (Box 353, Folder 40)
    - Advertising and Publicity (9401), 1966-71 (Box 353, Folder 41)
    - Travel (9301), 1966-71 (Box 353, Folder 42)
    - Supplies and Course and Teaching (9008), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 43)
    - Freight Charges (9407), 1966-69 (Box 354, Folder 44)
    - Telephone Rent (9201), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 45)
    - Publications - Educational Science (8403), 1966-69 (Box 354, Folder 46)
    - Convention Rentals (8601), 1967-71 (Box 354, Folder 47)
    - Postage (8101), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 48)
    - Supplies and Expenses (8105), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 49)
    - Cleaning Services (8203), 1967-70 (Box 354, Folder 50)
    - Equipment Office Furniture (7203), 1966-68 (Box 354, Folder 51)
    - Machine Maintenance (7808), 1967-71 (Box 354, Folder 52)
    - Supplies (8003), 1967-71 (Box 354, Folder 53)
    - Clerical Bureau Services (8106) (6644), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 54)
    - Groceries (6802), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 55)
    - Membership Dues (6901), 1966-71 (Box 354, Folder 56)
    - Periodical Subscriptions (6902), 1966-71 (Box 355, Folder 57)
    - Entertainment (7102), 1966-71 (Box 355, Folder 58)
    - Equipment -Furnishing (7201), 1966-69 (Box 355, Folder 59)
    - Repairs and Construction (7804), 1967-70 (Box 355, Folder 60)
    - Dining Hall (6810), 1967-71 (Box 355, Folder 61)
    - Printing and Copy Services (6506), 1967-71 (Box 355, Folder 62)
    - Books (6501), 1966-71 (Box 355, Folder 63)
    - Editorial Consultation (6207), 1966-71 (Box 355, Folder 64)
    - Honoraria (6205), 1967-71 (Box 355, Folder 65)
    - Tape Recording Supplies (6104), 1967 (Box 355, Folder 66)
    - Reference Room Records, 1970 (Box 355, Folder 67)
    - Proposal Submitted to United States Public Health for Combined Basic Graduate Program), 1971 (Box 355, Folder 68)
    - General Research Support Grant (RR05617-02), 1972-73 (Box 356, Folder 69)
    - Research Development Grant (NU 00314-05), 1971-73 (Box 356, Folder 70)
    - General Research support Grant (RR05617POl), 1971 (Box 356, Folder 71)
    - Clinical Record -Old Forms (samples), 1945-70 (Box 356, Folder 72)
    - Letters and Brochures for Trainees, 1960 (Box 356, Folder 73)
    - Recruitment -Visit to Yale School of Nursing by Counselors and Deans, 1951 (Box 356, Folder 74)
    - Publicity, 1946-47 (Box 356, Folder 75)
    - Replies to Publicity Letter to Colleges, 1947 (Box 357, Folder 76)
    - Recruitment Publicity, 1952-54 (Box 357, Folder 77)
    - Yale School of Nursing Advertisement for Master's Program, 1943 (Box 357, Folder 78)
    - Yale School of Nursing Enrollment and Clinical Records, 1946-47 (Box 357, Folder 79)
    - Publicity Folder (Miscellaneous Correspondence), 1941-42 (Box 357, Folder 80)
    - Role Development Project
      - Measures -Questionnaires -Scales (J. Barrett), 1966-1967 (Box 357, Folder 81)
      - Instructions for Nursing Action, Study and Code, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 82)
      - Nursing Activities Study Forms, 1968 (Box 357, Folder 83)
      - Work Table, 1970 (Box 357, Folder 84)
      - Patient Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 357, Folder 85)
      - Data Collected -Diaries, 1969-70 (Box 357, Folder 86)
      - Ward Diary (C. Phelps) Examples, 1970 (Box 357, Folder 87)
      - Data Collected and Preliminary Part Observations, 1970 (Box 357, Folder 88)
      - Forms Used, 1971 (Box 357, Folder 89)
      - Correspondence re: Award end Extensions, 1969 (Box 357, Folder 90)
      - Correspondence-Measures, 1970-11 (Box 357, Folder 91)
      - Prospective staff-correspondence, 1968-69 (Box 357, Folder 92)
      - Project Draft submitted to Faye Abdellah, 1967 (Box 357, Folder 93)
      - Budget -Annual Report, 1970 (Box 358, Folder 94)
      - Conferences with Staff Yale New Haven Hospital, 1969-70 (Box 358, Folder 95)
      - Data collected -Pt. Comment Letters -T5, 1970 (Box 358, Folder 96)
      - Correspondence -Cl. Nurse Spec., 1967 (Box 358, Folder 97)
      - Participants, 1971 (Box 358, Folder 98)
      - Activity Analysis, Analysis of Data, 1969 (Box 358, Folder 99)
    - Yale University School of Medicine: Committee on Hospital
      - Fourth Conference, 1972 (Box 358, Folder 100)
      - First Conference, 1969 (Box 358, Folder 101)
      - Second Conference, 1970 (Box 358, Folder 101)
      - Third Conference, 1970 (Box 358, Folder 101)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program (see Box 363, Folder 148)
      - Seven-Year March toward Medical Regionalization (Grant requests), 1973-74 (Box 358, Folder 102)
      - Progress Report for -1972-73 (Grant, and Supplementary Grant Requests), 1972-74 (Box 358, Folder 103)
      - The CRMP Story: Toward Improved Quality and Accessibility of Health Care, 1970-72 (Box 358, Folder 104)
      - Triennial Application and Progress Report (Grant request), 1969-74 (Box 358, Folder 105)
      - Progress Report and Supplementary Grant requests (Summary Ed.), 1970 (Box 358, Folder 106)
      - Request for a Supplemental Grant, Part I (Summary Ed.), 1970 (Box 359, Folder 107)
      - Progress Report for 1969 and Cont. Grant request with Summary Report, 1970 (Box 359, Folder 109)
      - Connecticut Pathways toward Partnership Planning and Programs, 1968 (Box 359, Folder 110)
      - Progress Report for 1969 and Cont. Grant request (Box 359, Folder 111-112)
      - Request for Operating Grant, 1968 (Box 359, Folder 113)
      - Conference starting YSN CRMP Regional Act, 1969 (Box 359, Folder 114)
      - SRMP 1970 Appendix A - YSN (Box 359, Folder 115)
    - Brainstorming Meeting, 1970 December 15 (Box 359, Folder 116)
    - American Nurses' Foundation Grant (F. Wald), 1970 (Box 359, Folder 117)
    - A Nurse's Study of the Care of Dying Patients, NU 00352-02, 1970-72 (Box 359, Folder 118)
    - A Nurse's Study of the Care of Dying Patients, NU 00352-02, 1970-71 (Box 360, Folder 119)
    - Interdisciplinary Study of Care for Dying Patients, ANF 2-70-023, 1970 (Box 360, Folder 120)
    - NU 00323-02 (9580-49-50772) Jean Barrett's grant, 1970-71 (Box 360, Folder 121)
    - NU ME 00370-01 (A. Slavinsky), 1970-71 (Box 360, Folder 122)
    - NIH 70-4001 Contract - Reports and minutes, 1970-71 (Box 360, Folder 123)
    - C.R.M.P. records
      - Grant Approvals and Financial Statements (CRMP-YSN), 1970-72 (Box 360, Folder 124)
      - Nursing School Project, 1969-70 (Box 360, Folder 125)
      - Nursing Faculty Proposal (RM 00008-01), 1969 (Box 360, Folder 126)
      - Nursing Faculty Proposal (RM 00008-02), 1970-71 (Box 360, Folder 127)
      - Nursing Faculty Proposal (RM 00008-03), 1971 (Box 361, Folder 128-129)
      - Proposal for 1972/74 (Box 361, Folder 130)
      - Nursing School Project 1971/72 (Box 361, Folder 131)
      - YSN-CRMP Project Report, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 132)
      - Nursing School Project 1970/71, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 133)
      - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1971-73 (Box 361, Folder 134)
      - South-West Area, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 135)
      - South-West Programs, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 136)
      - Grant Information, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 137)
      - Expenditures, 1970 (Box 362, Folder 138)
      - South-Central Questionnaires, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 139)
      - Bridgeport Area, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 140)
      - Bridgeport Leadership program-photograph, 1971 (Box 362, Folder 141)
      - Danbury Area, 1970 (Box 362, Folder 142)
      - Danbury Program, 1971 (Box 363, Folder 143)
      - South-Central Area, 1971-73 (Box 363, Folder 144)
      - YSN-CRMP Project -Final Report, 1973 (Box 363, Folder 145)
      - Introductions and Early CRMP History Nursing Project, 1969 (Box 363, Folder 146)
      - Survey, 1970 (Box 363, Folder 147)
      - Report of YSN-CRMP Project (written to answer questions), 1969-71 (Box 363, Folder 148)
      - YSN-CRMP Project (site visit), 1972 (Box 363, Folder 149)
      - Site visits, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 150)
      - YSN-CRMP Project Report, 1973 (Box 363, Folder 151)
      - Annual reports reo YSN-CRMP Project to YSN, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 152)
      - Report on YSN-CRMP Project to New England Council on Higher Education, 1972 (Box 363, Folder 153)
      - Problem-Oriented Medical Record Conference, 1973 (Box 363, Folder 154)
      - Clearinghouse information, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 155)
      - Library News, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 156)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 364, Folder 157)
      - U.Conn's perspective and Strategies for Change, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 158)
      - YSN Continuing Education Offerings, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 159)
      - Lower Naugatuck Valley Home Health Care (Request not answered), 1970-71 (Box 364, Folder 160)
      - Community Based Faculty, 1971 (Box 364, Folder 161)
      - Consultation Requests, 1971 (Box 364, Folder 162)
      - New England Council on Higher Education for Nursing, 1972-73 (Box 364, Folder 163)
      - Waterbury Neighborhood Center, 1970 (Box 364, Folder 164)
      - N. Best -Other activities, 1970-73 (Box 364, Folder 165)
      - Stoma Care Program, 1971-1972 (Box 364, Folder 166)
      - CORA -Committee on Regional Activities of the Medical School, 1972-73 (Box 364, Folder 167)
      - Nursing Home Traveling Library Study, 1973 (Box 364, Folder 168)
      - Magazine article on YSN-CRMP Project (Connecticut Nursing News), 1971 (Box 364, Folder 169)
      - Waterbury Hospital Model Unit, 1971 (Box 364, Folder 171)
      - Waterbury Area, 1972 (Box 364, Folder 172)
      - Faculty Advisory Committee on Continuing Education, 1972-73 (Box 365, Folder 173)